Did you call for me, Father?
I'm thinking about sending Kunon
to the school for noble children.
But Kunon hasn't...
Right. He's never been outside of the mansion
except for a handful of times since birth.
He'll be scared of strangers
in the outside world.
That's why I'm counting on you.
Wanna play outside for a change?
But I can't...
You'll be fine.
I'll hold your hand.
Understood, Father.
I'll protect Kunon at any cost.
As his big brother, no matter
what happens this time around!
What are you reading about?
Hydromancy.
You fill a container processed with
supernatural powers with water
and tell fortunes or look for missing items.
Can we look for my first flush of
youth and its brilliance that I've lost?!
Don't worry. You're young and right
in the middle of the bloom of youth.
Can we use that whatchamacallit-mancy
to find my groom-to-be?
You're a fine woman,
and men will be all over you.
If I weren't the second son of the marquess,
I'd take you as my bride.
Oh please, what are you saying to a woman
more than ten years older than you?
How are you so cheerful?
TO THE SCHOOL FOR NOBLE CHILDREN
Therefore, when creating a
settlement and populating it,
the top priority must be securing water.
An excellent answer.
I've given him lectures and taught
him manners as a noble gentleman.
And why not make him a gentleman
with a sense of humor?
But was I right?
A jolly man can be attractive,
and that suits Master Kunon better.
He may be seen as a bit shallow, but...
What's making you look concerned?
Here's to looking at you.
Okay, quite shallow.
But compared to when I met him,
he's become a lot more adorable.
This is a twelve-year vintage from the New
Kingdom, worthy of beautiful Lady Flora.
Enchanting aroma, isn't it?
Oh, no, it's not, Master Kunon.
This is from Hughlia. Domestic tea.
Never mind, then.
Shall we get going?
Lord Gurion is waiting for you.
Right.
It's cold!
Master Kunon,
can you make you-know-what?
Sure, no problem.
A-ori.
So warm! So squishy!
This feels so nice to the touch.
I encased water with a super soft
and stretchy membrane.
It's still a prototype, though.
I want a bed of this to sleep in!
I'm thinking about that, too.
By the way, I wonder what Father
would like to speak to me about.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't think you've done
anything to get yelled at.
You learned your lesson from
the sea of blood incident.
That was because you said,
"Then let's go all out."
That was a bit too far.
But I don't hate stuff like that.
Same here.
Master Kunon, we've been expecting you.
Good evening, Balen.
Hey, it's been a while.
Big Brother!
Want me to lead you by the hand?
I'm all right.
I can sense what's around
me pretty well now.
That's also your magic, huh?
Big Brother?
It's nothing. I'm glad you're doing great.
My lord, my lady, they are here.
Welcome, Kunon.
Good evening, Mother, Father.
There's something important to tell you.
Lady Flora told us you finished what they
cover at the school for noble children.
But aren't you interested in
going to the actual school?
I am not.
I'd hate to trouble those around me,
and I have something I want
to prioritize over school.
I've always believed you should
do what your heart desires.
Is there a problem if I don't go to school?
Noble children are obligated to go.
On paper, you are enrolled in
the school for noble children.
And that isn't enough?
Your circumstances are special,
so we have permission from His
Majesty for schooling to be optional.
I smell nepotism...
I don't appreciate that phrasing,
and that's beside the point.
Give it some thought.
About how to use my allowance, you mean?
No, not about your allowance!
But you always complain.
It may seem like a waste of money to you,
but I think I'm spending it responsibly!
Again, I'm not talking about your allowance!
Father, thank you for always working
hard to provide for the family!
Let's put that aside for now!
Are you still mad at me, then?
I'm sorry for turning your
garden into a sea of blood!
That was unacceptable!
Next time, no allowance for six months!
Dear, we're not here to talk
about that today.
I'm asking you to think
about Princess Mirika.
Her Highness?
Those who do not fulfill their noble obligations
are at a disadvantage in high society.
Because of you, Princess Mirika might be
viewed in a negative light in the future.
Very well. I'll go.
Honestly, I think it's a hassle.
I'm not asking you to go for years.
You just need to take the advancement exams.
The advancement exams?
Pass them, and you'll receive the
official certificate of graduation.
There are five exams, so you only
need to go to school five times.
That's easy.
Princess Mirika and I will graduate after the
next exam, so you'll be taking it with us.
If that's the case, let's get you
ready to go to school, Kunon.
Yes, Mother.
You'll need clothes, shoes, and a nice coat.
First, let's take your measurements.
Iko, I need your help.
Ixio.
There are other royals at school.
They may try to approach
Kunon and Princess Mirika.
Have no fear. I will be with them.
You're going to school?
Yes, though only for the advancement exams.
That is wonderful.
I get to spend time with you at school!
To tell you the truth, I don't really
know what to expect at school.
Don't worry!
I will escort you as your elder!
I'll take you up on that.
But I'm worried.
If Your Highness is with me, then all the boys
who are in love with you will be jealous of me.
What? Oh, I'm certain it will be fine...
Are you not popular?
Of course I am!
I am a princess, you know?!
There are boys who like me. As many as
the number of fingers on my right hand!
Right, so that's five.
Perhaps I'll get a new cane for self-defense.
Wow, so dashing!
Master Kunon, perhaps you were
the model for the classic storybook prince?
Alas, my true identity has been revealed.
I'm sorry for not telling you the truth.
Was my little brother always this shallow?
Prince, you're so handsome!
A-ori.
I am off.
Have a good day.
Have a good day!
Wow, it doesn't shake at all.
Father said a rough carriage
is bad for your back.
Magic is convenient.
Yes. Since it's so versatile, even I may
be able to find a job in the future.
Was that even a question?
I'm sure you're nervous to
travel far away from the house.
I wouldn't say that.
I've grown a bit stronger.
I know I've worried you a lot, too.
When I fell and hurt myself...
You blamed yourself for that, didn't you?
Kunon.
I'm all right now.
I used to wish I could just disappear, but
now I'm determined to survive no matter what.
I see.
He truly has changed since learning magic.
I have a drive that I want to prevail,
even if the rest of the world perishes!
Hmm?!
I'm sorry, Big Brother. But I will live.
I'll outlive everyone so thoroughly that
I feel bad for the whole human race!
Oh, okay...
I'm questioning if he really
is my little brother.
Maybe it's the influence of that maid?
Let's go!
Are we almost at school?
Wow, you can tell?
Yes, I sense a lot of people.
Kunon! Master Ixio!
Good morning, Your Highness.
May I have half of your day
so I can tell you how happy I am
to hear your beautiful voice
first thing in the morning?
Your bow tie is adorable.
Isn't it?
Oh, could it be that this is more
adorable than Your Highness?
It could never.
Good. If you had said yes, I would have
torn this off right here, right now.
What's up with these two?
Shall we go, then?
Kunon?
And then my cat...
Goodness, is that true?
Today's exam will cover...
That's really cute.
The presence of countless people
and endless voices...
My past self would have recoiled from this.
You Highness. May I become a girl just for now?
Very well. Then I shall become a boy.
Sweet young lady, may I have your hand?
It's almost time.
Good morning, Professor Kast.
Yes, good morning.
The second son of the marquess,
with the Hero's Scar.
I've heard rumors that he's a shy boy.
Can a novice teacher like me handle
the job of showing him around?
He's so charming! Like a prince!
But I don't remember
a student like that here.
Mr. Kunon Gurion!
Yes?
I am Kast, a professor at this school.
I'll be your guide today.
Wonderful. Nice to meet you, Professor Kast.
I am Kunon Gurion.
I'm a girl right now, so allow me to curtsy.
A girl?
Biologically a boy, with a personality of a boy.
But today, I'm a girl. A beautiful girl.
What does that mean?
And why did he add "beautiful"?
I'll see you later, Kunon.
We'll have lunch together.
Professor, I'll leave my brother in your care.
S-Sure.
Good day, Princess Mirika.
I'll see you later, Big Brother.
I've a feeling this will be a lot of work...
So that's the Hero's Scar, Kunon Gurion.
I hear he received blessings from His Majesty
as the first Hero's Scar born in 100 years.
Huh?
He doesn't seem like a big deal!
Right! Like a rolled-up roly-poly!
The Hero's Scar might just be
an unfounded superstition!
Tch.
Come on.
Yes, Prince Lyle.
Mr. Kunon Gurion. Did you hear the
overview of the advancement exams?
Yes. I was told that if I pass five exams,
I can receive the certificate of graduation.
That is correct.
Normally, after taking an exam, there will
be a period of time to prepare for the next.
As an exception, your exams
will be held in a shorter period.
Exception?
I've received orders from your
father and His Majesty to do so.
Professor.
My father and His Majesty are besties.
This is nepotism.
I apologize for pressuring
the school to do this.
I'm going to pretend I didn't hear that.
I hear these things happen
all the time in high society.
If anything is unclear, feel free to tell me.
They're thick as thieves.
Please begin.
My father and His Majesty, I mean.
I did say feel free to tell me, but please
do not involve me in a political mess.
This relationship has been going
on since the previous generation—
Start the exam.
I never expected him to continue
chit-chatting for the whole exam.
And look what you get.
This question, that question.
All the other subjects...
He got everything right?!
It doesn't make sense.
I'm famished.
What would you like to eat?
Mirika.
Your Highness?
Who is it?
Did this brat really receive
blessings from my father?
Brother Lyle!
Stay out of this, Mirika.
We were having a good time.
I don't care who it is, if they agonize
Her Highness and get in our way...
Did you want something with my
little brother, Prince Lyle?
This is disrespectful, scion of the Gurions.
I gave you no permission to speak.
That's right!
What His Highness said.
Get lost, big brother of the roly-poly.
Royalty approaching them on the first day?
And what the heck is the
big brother of the roly-poly?
A-ori.
Status is supposed to be irrelevant at school.
Let us smooth things over...
What's this? Did he wet himself?
Huh?
Prince Lyle?!
I-I didn't!
But that looks like...
Like you have...
I told you I didn't!
Come!
Yes, Your Highness!
A nuisance is gone.
What will you have, Big Brother?
I'd like a hamburger!
Hold up, hold up!
Kunon, that was you, wasn't it?
Princess Mirika, what will you have?
I'll have a hamburger!
Kunon...
So, who was that earlier?
My brother, one year above me.
Sixth Prince Lyle Hughlia.
Your Highness's big brother?
Are you serious?
Because there can't be a big brother who
doesn't cherish his little siblings!
I wish that was true.
Is this true, Big Brother?
It is.
I had no idea.
I'm glad that you're my big brother.
R-Right.
My little brother really has changed.
We acted so out of line to
someone so untouchable.
How should I report this to Father?
This is very good, Big Brother.
This is how Kunon is.
Rambling about it is not
going to change anything.
Let's enjoy our meal.
The hamburger is tasty.
Yes, it is!
It is the best one I've ever tasted.
Please let us graduate without
any further incident.
That's wonderful to hear.
It is unbelievable.
NEXT EPISODE:
GRADUATION, AND WHAT'S NEXT?
Next episode:
"Graduation, and What's Next?"